ILR School German Program /3068
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School German Program
1953-1954
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/3068
3.11 cubic feet
3.1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Correspondence, publications, training materials, and other files regarding the State Department Program for German Industrial Relations Trainees.
8436562
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, December 23, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /4224: John Windmuller Papers
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8436562
- State Department Program for German Industrial Relations Trainees 1953-54, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Attitude Test, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Illini Forum (German), 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Treffpunkt Madison, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 'Treffpunkt' Madison, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Illini Forum (German), 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Illini Forum, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Illini Forum, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Illini Forum (German), 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cornell University Messenger Service Radio + Elect., 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cornell University Messenger Service - Endicott Johnson + Misc. German (Box 1, Folder 11)
- State Department Program for German Industrial Relations Trainees, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- State Department Program for German Industrial Relations Trainees, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Magazines, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Magazines, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Corning Glass Works - Magazines, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Corning Glass Works - Magazines, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Books, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Univ. of Wisconsin, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Memos, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- German Program Application forms, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- German Trainees - 2nd Program, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Questionnaire - German I.R., 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- German Trainees - 1st Program, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- German Program - Questionnaire, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Uber'm Grossen Teich, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  German
- Uber'm Grossen Teich, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Uber'm Grossen Teich, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Across the Big Pond, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- USIS Feature (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Albany Trip, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Final Report on 1953-1954 Project for German Industrial Relations Trainees (Box 3, Folder 7)
  July 19, 1954
- State Department Program for German Industrial Relations Trainees, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Public Relations, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- ILR 93, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Fall 1953
- Spare Copies of Materials Sent to German Trainees for 3rd Program (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Spring Trip, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Memos: Hanson (Box 3, Folder 13)
- German Students: Shipping, Travel Instructions, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Memos to Dean Catherwood, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Certificates, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Committee on Friendly Relations, 1951-1954 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Field Trips, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- English Instruction, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Newspaper/Magazine (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Housing (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Immigration (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Manhattan, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Medical (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Memos: R. A. Morrison, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Wisconsin (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Illinois (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Christmas Vacation (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Travel Requests, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- ILR 95 Speakers (Box 3, Folder 31)
- State Department Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Reports, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Miscellaneous, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- The Study Group of German Labor Union Leaders and Administration Specialists (Box 4)